Donald T. Regan Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
Donald T. Regan Papers 1919-1993 1981-1987
MSS82740
Regan, Donald T.
78,000 items
221 containers plus 21 oversize plus 5 classified
95.2 linear feet
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Correspondence, memoranda, chronological and subject files, speeches and engagements file, personal file, scrapbooks, and other papers documenting Donald T. Regan's government service as U.S. secretary of the treasury and chief of White House staff during the presidency of Ronald Reagan.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Bush, George, 1924-2018.; Casey, William J.; Deaver, Michael K.; Gorbachev, Mikhail Sergeevich, 1931-; Leland, Marc Ernest, 1938-; McFarlane, Robert C.; McLaughlin, Ann Dore.; McNamar, Richard T.; Mehle, Roger W. (Roger William), 1941-; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.; Poindexter, John M.; Reagan, Nancy, 1921-2016.; Reagan, Ronald.; Regan, Donald T.; Sprinkel, Beryl W.; Stockman, David Alan, 1946-; Volker, Paul.
Organizations
Board of Governors of the Federal Reserve System (U.S.); Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs (U.S.); Council of Economic Advisers (U.S.); United States Mint.; United States. Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms.; United States. Department of the Treasury.; United States. Office of Management and Budget.; United States. Secret Service.; United States. White House Office.
Subjects
Finance, Public--United States.; Summit meetings--Iceland--Reykjavík.; Summit meetings--Switzerland--Geneva.
Places
Soviet Union--Foreign relations--United States.; United States--Economic policy.; United States--Foreign relations--Soviet Union.
Occupations
Cabinet officers.; Financiers.; Public officials.
Acquisition Information
The papers of Donald T. Regan, cabinet member, White House chief of staff, and financier, were deposited in the Library of Congress by Regan in 1994.
Transfers
Items have been transferred from the Manuscript Division to other custodial divisions of the Library. Some photographs have been transferred to the Prints and Photographs Division. Sound and video recordings have been transferred to the Motion Picture, Broadcasting, and Recorded Sound Division. All transfers are identified in these divisions as part of the Donald T. Regan Papers.
Access and Restrictions
The papers of Donald T. Regan are open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Security Classified Documents
Government regulations control the use of security classified items in this collection. Manuscript Division staff can furnish information concerning access to and use of classified material.
Biographical Note
Date Event
1918, Dec. 21 Born, Cambridge, Mass.
1940 B.A., Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
1940 1946 Served in United States Marine Corps, becoming lieutenant colonel Posted to Iceland and participated in Guadalcanal, New Georgia, North Solomons, Guam, and Okinawa operations in the Pacific
1942 Married Ann Gordon Buchanan
1946 Entered training program, Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner, and Beane
1968 President, Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner, and Smith
1970 1980 Member, board of trustees, University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Pa. (chairman 1974-1978)
1971 Elected chairman of the board and chief executive officer, Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner, and Smith
1972 Published A View from the Street (New York: New American Library. 220 pp.)
1972 1975 Vice chairman, director, New York Stock Exchange
1981 Resigned from Merrill Lynch and Co.
1981 1985 Secretary of the treasury
1985 1987 White House chief of staff
1987 1994 President, Regdon Associates, Alexandria, Va.
1987 1989 Commentator, NBC News and NBC Radio Network
1988 Published For the Record: From Wall Street to Washington (New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich. 397 pp.)
2003, June 10 Died, Williamsburg, Va.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of Donald Thomas Regan (1918- 2003) span the years 1919-1993, with the bulk of the collection dating from the period 1981-1987, the years in which Regan served first as secretary of the treasury and then White House chief of staff during the presidency of Ronald Reagan. Regan's career at Merrill Lynch and Company started with a training program following his military service in World War II and culminated as chief executive officer and chairman of the board. His papers, focusing mainly on his government service in the Reagan administration, are organized into three series: Treasury Department, White House, and a Personal File.
The Treasury Department series contains files from Regan's tenure as secretary of the treasury from January 1981 to January 1985. It is the largest segment of the collection and documents the economic policies of the Reagan administration. Chronological files within the series include Regan's official correspondence and a reading and information file containing material put together by Regan's executive assistant, David L. Chew, to brief the secretary on important issues and activities. Another subseries contains memoranda prepared by various offices in the Treasury Department, including those relating to domestic finance, economic policy, monetary affairs, and tax policy. A speeches and engagements file contains a chronological record of the speaking engagements, statements, and trips Regan made as secretary.
The subject file in the Treasury Department series focuses on the issues, activities, and organization relating to the Treasury Department during Regan's tenure. It includes files on the bureaus comprising the department, such as the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms, the Secret Service, and the United States Mint, as well as economic policy-making bodies such as the Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs, the Council of Economic Advisors, the Federal Reserve Board, and the Office of Management and Budget. A file of transition material contains briefing books on economic issues addressed at the start of the Reagan administration. Additional subjects covered include the federal budget, financial deregulation, tax cut legislation, and tax reform. Filed with material on the thrift industry are papers relating to a congressional inquiry into savings and loan institutions which took place in 1991 when Regan testified regarding policies and activities during his term as secretary of the treasury.
Individuals whose activities and correspondence are reflected in the Treasury Department files include department officials Marc Leland,; Ann Dore McLaughlin,; Richard T. McNamar,; Roger W. Mehle, and Beryl W. Sprinkel; director of the Office of Management and Budget; David Alan Stockman; head of the Federal Reserve; Paul Volker; and Vice President George Bush.
In January 1985, at the start of Ronald Reagan's second term, Donald Regan and James A. Baker switched positions, with Baker becoming secretary of the treasury and Regan taking over as White House chief of staff. Papers in Regan's White House files relate to his service until his resignation on 27 February 1987. Regan's management of the day-to-day operations of the Reagan presidency is documented in the daily schedules of both Regan and the president and Regan's telephone logs of incoming and outgoing calls. Notes recording the activities and issues dealt with by the White House, including notes on meetings and conversations, are also among Regan's files.
A subject file in the White House series includes administrative and briefing documents related to Regan's appointment as chief of staff. One such document is a letter from Richard Nixon offering his impressions and advice on running the White House. Another subject treated is arms control negotiations with the Soviet Union, including files on summit meetings in Geneva, Switzerland, and Reykjavik, Iceland. Located in files relating to the Soviet Union is an exchange of correspondence between Ronald Reagan and Mikhail Gorbachev that occurred in the period between these summit meetings. There is also material on the Iran-Contra Affair, some of which, along with files for his memoirs, was subpoenaed during an independent counsel's investigation into the Iran-Contra Affair. Notations and markers are attached to documents requested and examined in 1992 as part of this inquiry.
Individuals mentioned in the White House series are William Casey,; Michael Deaver,; Robert C. "Bud" McFarlane,; John M. Poindexter, and Nancy Reagan.
The Personal File contains material related to Regan's activities outside government before and after his positions in the Reagan administration, including a few items from his career at Merrill Lynch. These files supplement a larger collection of records, including fifty-six volumes of desk diaries, schedule books, and calendars dating from 1952 to 1980, which is located in the Merrill Lynch corporate archives in New York. Other papers from the period prior to Regan's work in Washington include files of political activities and memberships in organizations ranging from the tournament policy board of the Professional Golfers' Association of America to his chairmanship of the board of trustees of the University of Pennsylvania.
Files from the period following his departure from government service include speeches and writings. Files from the preparation of his memoirs For the Record, which he wrote with the assistance of Charles McCarry, include transcripts of tapes which Regan dictated, communications with and drafts by McCarry, and research files containing such original documents from Regan's Treasury Department and White House periods as a diary of his initial days as secretary of the treasury, his handwritten account of the assassination attempt on President Reagan in 1981, as well as notes from that day, material on Reagan's cancer surgery in 1985, and the Geneva summit meeting. Among the speeches and writings are commentaries, mainly on financial topics, which Regan presented on television and radio. Papers relating to Thomas Dawson, Regan's executive assistant at the White House who moved with him to the firm Regan established, Regdon Associates, also appear among Regan's personal files.
Organization of the Papers
The collection is arranged in five series:
Treasury Department, 1975-1992
White House, 1947-1993
Personal File, 1919-1993
Classified, 1979-1987
Top Secret, 1987
Container List
- Treasury Department, 1975-1992 (Box 1-188)
  - Chronological Files, 1981-1985 (Box 1-29)
    Official and personal correspondence sent by Regan with attached material, a reading file of memoranda and notes from Regan's staff with attached related material, and a file of notes to staff.
    Arranged by type of material and chronologically therein.
    - Official (Box 1)
      - 9 Jan.-18 Mar. 1981, (7 folders)
      - 20 Mar.-19 May 1981, (9 folders) (Box 2)
      - 20 May-15 July 1981, (7 folders) (Box 3)
      - 16 July-24 Sept. 1981, (7 folders) (Box 4)
      - 25 Sept.-30 Nov. 1981, (7 folders) (Box 5)
      - 2 Dec. 1981-11 Feb. 1982, (7 folders) (Box 6)
      - 12 Feb.-31 Mar. 1982, (7 folders) (Box 7)
      - 1 Apr.-18 June 1982, (7 folders) (Box 8)
      - 21 June-19 Aug. 1982, (6 folders) (Box 9)
      - 20 Aug.-19 Nov. 1982, (8 folders) (Box 10)
      - 22 Nov. 1982-31 Jan. 1983, (7 folders) (Box 11)
      - 1 Feb.-25 Mar. 1983, (7 folders) (Box 12)
      - 28 Mar.-25 May 1983, (6 folders) (Box 13)
      - 26 May-30 June 1983, (7 folders) (Box 14)
      - 1 July-11 Aug. 1983, (7 folders) (Box 15)
      - 12 Aug.-15 Nov. 1983, (7 folders) (Box 16)
      - 16 Nov. 1983-28 Feb. 1984, (7 folders) (Box 17)
      - 1 Mar.-15 May 1984, (7 folders) (Box 18)
      - 16 May-23 July 1984, (7 folders) (Box 19)
      - 24 July-31 Oct. 1984, (6 folders) (Box 20)
      - 2 Jan.-1 Feb. 1985, (6 folders) (Box 21)
    - Personal (Box 22)
      - 22 Jan. 1981-14 Jan. 1985, (8 folders)
    - Reading and information (Box 23)
      - 4 Jan.-31 July 1982, (8 folders)
      - 3 Aug. 1982-28 Feb. 1983, (8 folders) (Box 24)
      - 1 Mar.-23 Dec. 1983, (7 folders) (Box 25)
      - 5 Jan.-16 Apr. 1984, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Staff notes
      - 24 May-10 Nov. 1983, (5 folders)
      - 14 Nov. 1983-12 Apr. 1984, (6 folders) (Box 27)
      - 16 Apr.-31 Oct. 1984, (6 folders) (Box 28)
      - 2 Nov. 1984-31 Jan. 1985, (3 folders) (Box 29)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 29-34)
    Letters received by Regan.
    Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent.
    - A, 1980-1984 (Box 29)
    - B, 1982-1985, (3 folders)
    - C, 1982-1985 (Box 30)
    - D, 1981-1984, (2 folders)
    - E, 1981-1984
    - F, 1981-1985, (2 folders)
    - G, 1981-1984, (4 folders)
    - H, 1980-1985, (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - I-J, 1981-1984
    - K, 1981-1984, (2 folders)
    - L, 1981-1985, (3 folders)
    - M, 1981-1985, (3 folders) (Box 32)
    - N, 1981-1984
    - O, 1981-1985
    - P, 1981-1984, (3 folders)
    - R, 1980-1984, (3 folders) (Box 33)
    - S, 1982-1985
    - T, 1981-1983, (2 folders)
    - U-V, 1981-1984
    - W, 1980-1984, (3 folders) (Box 34)
    - Y-Z, 1981-1984
  - Memoranda, 1981-1985 (Box 34-65)
    Memoranda received by individuals in the Treasury Department and other government officials.
    Arranged alphabetically by name of office or individual and chronologically therein.
    - Administration (Box 34)
      - Apr. 1981-Dec. 1982, (4 folders)
      - Jan. 1983-Jan. 1985, (7 folders) (Box 35)
    - Business and consumer affairs (Box 36)
      - Apr. 1982-May 1984, (6 folders)
      - June-Dec. 1984, (7 folders) (Box 37)
      - Jan. 1985 (Box 38)
    - Chew, David L., 1981-1984, (2 folders)
    - Deputy secretary, 1982-1985
    - Domestic finance
      - Feb. 1981-Mar. 1982, (4 folders)
      - Apr. 1982-Sept. 1983, (7 folders) (Box 39)
      - Oct. 1983-Apr. 1984, (7 folders) (Box 40)
      - May 1984-Jan. 1985, (8 folders) (Box 41)
    - Economic policy (Box 42)
      - Feb. 1981-Mar. 1982, (7 folders)
      - Apr. 1982-Aug. 1983, (8 folders) (Box 43)
      - Sept. 1983-Apr. 1984, (6 folders) (Box 44)
      - May 1984-Jan. 1985, (6 folders) (Box 45)
    - Electronic systems and information technology, 1982-1984
    - Enforcement and operations (Box 46)
      - Feb. 1981-Apr. 1984, (8 folders)
      - May 1984-Jan. 1985, (2 folders) (Box 47)
    - Entin, Stephen
      - 1981-1983, (5 folders)
      - 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - Executive secretariat, 1981-1984, (5 folders)
    - Fiscal, 1981-1985, (3 folders) (Box 49)
    - General counsel
      - Feb. 1981-Nov. 1983, (5 folders)
      - Dec. 1983-Jan. 1985, (4 folders) (Box 50)
    - Inspector general, 1981-1984, (2 folders)
    - International affairs
      - Jan. 1981-June 1982, (2 folders)
      - July 1982-Jan. 1985, (8 folders) (Box 51)
    - Legislative affairs (Box 52)
      - Jan. 1981-Mar. 1983, (6 folders)
      - Apr.-Oct. 1983, (6 folders) (Box 53)
      - Nov. 1983-Feb. 1984, (7 folders) (Box 54)
      - Mar. 1984-Jan. 1985, (8 folders) (Box 55)
    - Memoranda for the record, 1984 (Box 56)
    - Monetary affairs, 1981-1985, (7 folders)
    - Porter, Roger B., 1981-1984, (4 folders) (Box 57)
    - Public affairs
      - Jan.-Sept. 1981, (3 folders)
      - Oct. 1981-Oct. 1983, (7 folders) (Box 58)
      - Nov. 1983-Jan. 1985, (6 folders) (Box 59)
    - Staff, 1981-1984, (2 folders)
    - Tax and economic affairs, 1981-1982 (Box 60)
    - Tax policy
      - Jan. 1981-Aug. 1982, (6 folders)
      - Sept. 1982-Dec. 1983, (6 folders) (Box 61)
      - Jan. 1984-Jan. 1985, (7 folders) (Box 62)
    - Treasurer's office, 1981-1985, (4 folders) (Box 63)
    - White House
      - Baker, James A., 1984-1985
      - Fuller, Craig
        - 1981-1982, (3 folders)
        - 1983-1984, (3 folders) (Box 64)
      - Meese, Edwin, 1981-1984, (2 folders)
      - Reagan, Ronald
        - Incoming, 1981-1984
        - Outgoing
          - 1981, (2 folders)
          - 1982-1984, (7 folders) (Box 65)
  - Scrapbooks (Oversize), 1981-1985 (Box 66-87)
    Scrapbooks containing correspondence, photographs, clippings, and other memorabilia from Regan's tenure as secretary of the treasury.
    All but one of these volumes are arranged chronologically.
    - 1-31 Jan. 1981 (Box 66)
    - 1 Feb.-30 Mar. 1981 (Box 67)
    - 1-30 Apr. 1981 (Box 68)
    - 1 May-7 June 1981 (Box 69)
    - 7 June-20 July 1981 (Box 70)
    - 20 July-16 Sept. 1981 (Box 71)
    - 21 Sept.-31 Oct. 1981 (Box 72)
    - 1-30 Nov. 1981 (Box 73)
    - 1 Dec. 1981-31 Jan. 1982 (Box 74)
    - 1 Feb.-23 Mar. 1982 (Box 75)
    - 15 Apr.-18 May 1982 (Box 76)
    - 18 May-9 June 1982 (Box 77)
    - 10 June-21 Dec. 1982 (Box 78)
    - 20 Jan.-27 Apr. 1983 (Box 79)
    - 5-30 May 1983 (Box 80)
    - 1 June-18 July 1983 (Box 81)
    - 30 Jan.-30 Sept. 1983 (Box 82)
    - 3 Oct.-20 Dec. 1983 (Box 83)
    - 4 Jan.-30 Apr. 1984 (Box 84)
    - 2 Apr.-24 Dec. 1984 (Box 85)
    - 10-21 Jan. 1985 (Box 86)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 1981-1984 (Box 87)
  - Speech and Engagement File, 1981-1985 (Box 88-99)
    Speeches, statements, testimony, correspondence, and miscellaneous material relating to speaking engagements, trips, and other official activities undertaken by Regan.
    Arranged chronologically by event.
    - General (Box 88)
      - 27 Jan.-18 May 1981, (7 folders)
      - 17 June 1981-27 Jan. 1982, (6 folders) (Box 89)
      - 2 Feb.-26 Apr. 1982, (7 folders) (Box 90)
      - 3 May-27 July 1982, (8 folders) (Box 91)
      - 2 Aug.-26 Oct. 1982, (7 folders) (Box 92)
      - 4 Nov. 1982-21 Mar. 1983, (6 folders) (Box 93)
      - 6 Apr.-22 July 1983, (8 folders) (Box 94)
      - 8 Sept. 1983-31 Jan. 1984, (7 folders) (Box 95)
      - 1 Feb.-29 Apr. 1984, (7 folders) (Box 96)
      - 8 May-27 Sept. 1984, (8 folders) (Box 97)
      - 4 Oct. 1984-9 Jan. 1985, (3 folders) (Box 98)
    - Notebooks
      - Statements and speeches, 6 Jan.-6 Dec. 1981, (3 folders)
      - Testimony and speeches, 4 Feb.-26 Sept. 1984, (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - Subject File, 1975-1992 (Box 99-188)
    Correspondence, memoranda, briefing books, minutes, transcripts, reports, schedules, notes, clippings, charts, and printed matter.
    Arranged alphabetically by name of organization, topic, or activity.
    - Accomplishments, 1982-1983 (Box 99)
    - Acting secretaries, correspondence signed
      - McNamar, Richard T., 1982-1984, (4 folders)
      - Sprinkel, Beryl W., 1982-1984
    - Advisory Committee on International Monetary System (Fowler Committee), 1977-1984 (Box 100)
    - Appointments and schedules
      - Daily log
        - 1981-1982, (5 folders)
        - 1983-1985, (5 folders) (Box 101)
      - Schedules, 1981-1985, (3 folders) (Box 102)
    - Appropriations, 1981-1983, (3 folders)
    - Argentina, 1984
    - Asian Development Bank, 1983-1984
    - Automobile industry For additional material see Containers 131-132, Chrysler Corp. (Box 103)
      - Auto Industry Task Force, 1981, undated, (5 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1982-1983
    - Awards, 1981-1984
    - Banking See also Containers 147-148, Financial deregulation
      - Bank Holding Co. Act of 1983, 1983, undated, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1984 (Box 104)
    - Bonds, 1984, undated, (2 folders)
    - Brazil, 1982-1984, (2 folders)
    - Briefing papers
      - Jan.-Sept. 1981, (4 folders)
      - Oct. 1981-July 1982, (6 folders) (Box 105)
      - Aug.-Dec. 1982, (4 folders) (Box 106)
    - Budget
      - Capital budgeting, 1982-1983
      - Deficit, 1981-1984, undated, (3 folders); (8 folders) (Box 107)
      - Fiscal year (Box 108)
        - 1982
          - Fall budget program, 1981, undated, (2 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1981, undated, (2 folders)
        - 1983
          - Gang of seventeen budget strategy group, 1982, (3 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1982, undated, (5 folders) (Box 109)
          - Special negotiations, 1983
        - 1984 budget miscellany, 1983, undated, (3 folders) (Box 110)
        - 1985
          - Budget review board, 1983, (2 folders)
          - Midsession review, 1982-1984
          - Miscellany, 1983-1984, undated, (3 folders) (Box 111)
          - T-1 work, 1983-1984, (2 folders)
        - 1986
          - Briefing book, 1984, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 112)
          - Miscellany, 1984, undated, (4 folders)
      - Gramm-Latta bill, 1981, undated, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1983-1984, (4 folders) (Box 113)
      - Mondale, Walter, program, 1984, (3 folders)
      - Projections, 1981-1982 (Box 114)
      - Strategy, 1980-1981, (3 folders)
      - Treasury Department, 1982-1984, (2 folders)
    - Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms, 1981-1983, (2 folders)
    - Bureau of Engraving and Printing, 1981-1983 (Box 115)
    - Business Roundtable, 1981-1982
    - Cabinet councils
      - Commerce and trade
        - Mar. 1981-Mar. 1982, (5 folders)
        - Apr. 1982-Dec. 1983, (6 folders) (Box 116)
        - Feb.-Dec. 1984, (2 folders) (Box 117)
      - Economic affairs
        - Mar.-June 1981, (3 folders)
        - July-Dec. 1981, (6 folders) (Box 118)
        - Jan.-Mar. 1982, (6 folders) (Box 119)
        - Apr.-July 1982, (6 folders) (Box 120)
        - Aug.-Dec. 1982, Apr.-July 1982; (8 folders) (Box 121)
        - Jan.-July 1983, (7 folders) (Box 122)
        - Aug.-Nov. 1983, (6 folders) (Box 123)
        - Dec. 1983-Apr. 1984, (6 folders) (Box 124)
        - May-Dec. 1984, (7 folders) (Box 125)
        - Jan. 1985, undated, (3 folders) (Box 126)
      - Food and agriculture, 1982-1984, (2 folders)
      - Human resources
        - Feb.-Apr. 1982
        - June 1982-May 1984, (2 folders) (Box 127)
      - Legal policy, 1982-1983, (2 folders)
      - Management and administration, 1982-1984, (4 folders)
      - Natural resources and environment, 1982-1984, (4 folders) (Box 128)
    - Cabinet meetings
      - Jan. 1981-June 1982, (4 folders)
      - July 1982-Dec. 1984, (7 folders) (Box 129)
      - Jan. 1985 (Box 130)
    - Canada, 1981-1984
    - Charts, 1981-1984, (6 folders)
    - China, 1981-1984 See also Container 155, Joint commissions and committees (Box 131)
    - Chrysler Corp.
      - 1981, (6 folders)
      - 1982-1983, (4 folders) (Box 132)
    - Committees, 1975-1982, (2 folders)
    - Comptroller of the Currency
      - 1981-1983, (2 folders)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 133)
    - Congressional matters, 1981-1983, (2 folders)
    - Continental Illinois National Bank and Trust Co., Chicago, Ill., 1983-1984
    - Correspondence logs
      - Jan. 1981-May 1982, (4 folders)
      - June 1982-Jan. 1985, (6 folders) (Box 134)
    - Council of Economic Advisors
      - June 1981-June 1982, (2 folders)
      - July 1982-Jan. 1984, (7 folders) (Box 135)
      - Feb.-Dec. 1984 (Box 136)
    - Customs, 1981-1984, (3 folders)
    - Davis-Bacon Act, 1981
    - Debt ceiling, 1981-1984, (3 folders)
    - Debt management, 1982-1983, (2 folders)
    - Defense Department, 1981 (Box 137)
    - Denmark, 1982
    - Development Committee, 1982-1984, undated
    - Economic policy miscellany, 1981-1984, undated, (6 folders)
    - Economic recovery program, 1980-1981, undated For additional material see Containers 174-176, Legislation, (6 folders) (Box 138)
    - Economic situation, 1981-1984, undated, (7 folders); (6 folders) (Box 139, Box 140)
    - Economic summits
      - Cancun, Mexico, 1981, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 141)
      - London, England, 1984
      - Ottawa, Canada, 1981, (4 folders)
      - Versailles, France, 1982, (3 folders) (Box 142)
      - Williamsburg, Va., 1982-1983, (4 folders)
    - Energy, 1979-1982 (Box 143)
    - Eurobonds, 1984, (3 folders)
    - Exports
      - Coordinating Committee for Strategic Export Controls (COCOM), 1984